你找到几个弹壳?
How many shells you got?
拜托 拜托!
Come on, come on!
再来一个袋子
Another bag here.
老天
Christ.
警司?
Sergeant?
嗯?
Yeah?
主要负责人是谁?
Who are the primaries?
Cole和Norris Cole在这里...
Cole and Norris. Cole's here...
Norris在医院里
And Norris is at the hospital.
你需要什么?
What do you need?
干活的空间
Room to work.
我一直在命令大家撤离现场...
I keep ordering people off the scene...
缉毒科 药管局和两个区的...
And between Narcotics, DEA and the two districts...
汇聚到这里的人越来越多
We keep collecting more and more bodies around here.
谁都不许动!
Nobody move!
我说 他妈的谁都不许动!
I said, nobody fucking move!
如果你没有由一名凶杀科警探指派明确任务
If you haven't been assigned a specific task by a homicide detective...
你就得撤离犯罪现场
You need to step away from this crime scene.
有人听不懂直接命令吗
Is there anybody doesn't understand a direct order?
如果你没有接到其他明确指令
If you have not specifically been instructed otherwise...
那么滚出去吧 别在这里碍手碍脚
Then remove your useless interfering asses from the area.
就现在!
Now!
这事儿要慢慢来
Slow this thing down to a crawl.
别让那些混账东西把重要线索搞砸了
Give these bastards no chance to fuck up in a meaningful way.
好的
Okay.
卡在很后面
Wedged all the way to the back.
她够不着
She couldn't get to it.
她把枪粘在比较前面
She taped it up front...
但是她一坐上这些破烂座位
But as soon as she put any weight on these worn-ass car seats...
胶布就掉了
They pulled the tape off.
或许他们一开车 枪就滑到座位后面去了
Gun slid back behind the mesh as they drove, probably.
老天
Christ.
她的后援在哪里
Where was her support?
有两辆车在几个街区外跟着
There were two follow cars several blocks distant.
她的车在小巷里七弯八拐
She got turned around in the alleys.
她报告的位置是Warwick北边
She gave her 20 as the north side of Warwick.
枪击时他们赶去了那里?
They went there on the shots?
是直升机最终发现了她
The Foxtrot finally found her.
嘿 你得赶快撤离 快走
Hey, you got to be moving outta here.
所以说我们有两小队包围了北面 上面还有一架直升机
So, we had two units covering the north side and a helicopter up on top.
却没人看见逃逸车辆
And no one saw any vehicles in flight.
Bunk
Bunk.
Terry  Mike 来
Terry, Mike, come on.
他妈的怎么回事
What the fuck happened?
火线重案组 第一季 第十一集 追捕
The Wire S01E011 The Hunt
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
他妈的毒品摆桌上  ——Daniels
你们没有目击吗
You didn't have an eyeball?
在那些街道上 是不可能目击到的
On those streets, there's no way you can eyeball it.
她已经尽力汇报所在位置
She threw out 20s as best she could.
明白 我只是问问
Understood, I'm just asking.
我们的线索是Savino Bratton
The link we have to this is Savino Bratton.
我们的目标Barksdale的一名小喽啰
A minor lieutenant to our target, Barksdale.
这些我在现场就都告诉你们了
I gave your people that at the scene.
我们在搜查他最后已知的所在地 我们在办
We're hitting his last knowns. We're on that.
那伙人不止他一个人
The set-up was more than him.
弹壳的口径不同 她的防弹衣上都是洞
The casings are different calibers, and her Glock was full up.
有多糟?
How bad?
胸部中枪 子弹没有射出
Chest wound, no exit.
一直射到咽喉 她还尚未稳定
Through and through to the throat. She wasn't stabilized.
他们给她穿上了加压裤
They had the pressure pants on her.
想提高脉搏频率
Trying to push up the pulse.
一旦他们给你穿上那种裤子 情况就不妙了
They put those pants on you, it ain't good.
当你听到枪声时你在Baker街 第二辆车在哪里
You're on Baker when you hear the shots. Where was the second car?
- Warwick大道吧 我想 - 好的
- Warwick, I think. - Okay.
东边你们严密包围 西面是铁轨
You've got the east well-covered to the west is the rail bed.
直升机看到了什么
What did Foxtrot see?
除了我们的人 没有其他移动的车辆
Nothing moving except our units.
警督
Lieutenant...
我感同身受
I know just how you feel.
这是作为一名警局官员最困难的工作
This is the toughest job a police commissioner has.
我想我永远都习惯不了
I don't think I'll ever get used to it.
这位才是Daniels警督
This is Lieutenant Daniels.
哦对 对 当然
Right, of course.
整个警局都会全力支持Greggs警探
This entire department stands behind Detective Greggs...
在每一个可能的方面
In every possible way.
我只是想该让你知道
I just thought you should know that.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
Jaybird
Jaybird.
我们找到了个跑路的
We have a runner.
嗯 我们需要这两个脚印的模型
Yeah, we're gonna need casts of these two imprints.
这事儿交给实验室技术员
Put the lab tech on it.
11-39
11-39.
钱不是我们首要关心的问题 这个我懂
The money's not anyone's primary concern. I understand that.
我不会装作自己很在乎那些钱 因为你们失去了...
I'm not going to be standing giving a shit about the money when you have lost...
一名你们的同事可能....
One of your own who might....
我是说 天啊 真是糟透了
I mean, Jesus, this is awful.
另一方面 如果我们可以迅速抓到Savino这个家伙...
- If we can get to this Savino character-- - Hey.
操你的钱
Fuck your money.
Jimmy
Jimmy?
你受伤了吗
You hurt?
没有
No.
是她的血
It's hers.
好了 起来吧
Come on, get up.
走吧 快起来
Let's go, up with you.
来吧
Come on.
不能说话 不能呼吸
Couldn't talk, couldn't breathe.
什么都不能
Nothing.
她就这样进了救护车
She went into the ambo that way.
她是不是....
Is she....
他妈的我干了啥
What the fuck did I do?
好了 走一走
Come on, walk.
那是啥
What's that?
我们的计划是啥 Ray?
What's our plan, Ray?
Bunk和Jay留在现场
Bunk and Jay stay with the scene.
Keeley和Crutchfield在办公室
Keeley and Crutchfield are at the office
打印Savino那个混蛋的搜捕令
Typing warrants for Savino.
- 谁去做尸检 - 我 我去太平间
- Who's on the autopsy? - Me, I'm at the morgue.
Norris和Holley留在休克重伤室 以防她醒来开口说话
Norris and Holley stay at shock trauma in case she sits up and talks.
我们会用激光检测这辆车的指纹吧
We're laser printing the car, right?
当然 Worden会办的
'Course, Worden's on that.
您是市局的负责人 对吗
You're in command for the city, right?
Rawls警长 凶杀科
Major Rawls, Homicide.
袖章"DEA" :司法部药品管理局
如果您需要我们部的什么东西
Anything you need from my office...
人手 资金 任何东西 只管开口
Men, money, whatever, you just ask.
行
Right.
伙计 你们的姑娘躺在休克重伤室
Cooperator, your girl's down in shock trauma.
我们开工吧
Let's get to work.
你去死吧
Fuck you.
我去死?
Fuck me?
- 我们监听线开着呢 - 那又怎样
- We got a wire up. - So?
所以我们正监听着某个刚打了警察的混蛋
So we got a wire up on some motherfucker that just shot a cop.
如果有人谈论今晚这里发生的事
If somebody talks, and gets on the wrong phone...
并且用了不该用的电话 说了不该说的话
Says the wrong thing about what happened here tonight,
你们它妈的想候在哪儿?
Where the fuck do you want to be?
教堂顶上?
Church roof?
嗯 我和你
Yeah, you and me.
Sydnor盯着McCullough街上的电话亭
Sydnor takes the McCullough Street phone.
有人联系过Kima的亲友吗
Anybody get in contact with Kima's people?
妈的
Shit.
我先把那事儿办了 然后去教堂和你会合
I'll do that first, then meet you at the church.
Bunk  Mike
Bunk, Mike.
此人为Little Man
真不知道那婊子是谁
Wonder who that bitch was.
- 老是出娄子 是吧 - 嗯
- Always some shit, right? - Yeah.
- 搞定? - 搞定
- Done? - Done.
好了
All right.
我们走吧
Let's get outta here.
嗯
Yeah.
叫实验室技术员赶到这里 提取照片和模型
Lab tech to this spot. Photos and casts.
- 11-39 - 11-35
- 11-39. - 11-35.
可以让18-12过来吗
Can I get 18-12 up here?
嗯
Yeah.
你守在这里
You're camped here.
不准任何人碰这玩意儿 连靠近都不行
Nobody touches this shit, or even comes near it...
直到技术员做完复原
Until the tech does his recovery.
嘿
Hello.
他不跑了
He stopped running.
- 要么他累了... - 要么他坐上了一辆车
- Either he got tired or-- - Or he got into a car.
嗯
Right.
- 11-34 - 请讲 11-34
- 11-34. - Go ahead, 11-34.
我在...
I'm in the...
Landvale 3000号街区
3000 block of Landvale.
CSX 一家铁路营运公司
CSX铁轨后面
Backing up to the CSX bed.
我需要一实验室小队 和带手钻的公用事业局工人
I need a lab unit, and a DPW crew with a jackhammer.
手钻?
A jackhammer?
要保留一点路面啊 总台
Gonna keep a bit of road, KGA.
还活着 在手术室
Alive. In the OR.
我的人已经在现场听过这个了
My people at the scene have heard this.
- 这是原声带的拷贝 - 好的
- It's a copy of the original. - Okay.
我们把机器带来了...
We brought a machine--
- 他妈的在哪儿... - 长官
- Where the fuck is-- - Sir.
在这儿呢 嗯 放这儿吧
Here it is, here. Yeah, put it there.
"他妈的别少了数"
Don't fuck with this count.
这是Savino
That's Savino.
"我马上带你的东西回来"
I'll be right back with your shit.
"我们在哪儿?"
Where are we?
"路标说是Longwood 但我发誓这是Warwick"
That sign said Longwood, but I could swear this is Warwick.
"那些混混就喜欢弄乱路牌糊弄人"
Hoppers be turning the sign poles to fuck with you all.
"我觉得我们在Warwick北端 一条巷子里...."
I make it we're on the north side of Warwick, in an alley,
"我不知道 见鬼..."
I don't know, shit...
"Longwood向西半个街区 也许是"
Half a block west of Longwood, maybe?
"希望你们都听到了"
I hope you all copy that.
"你感觉对头吗"
This got the right feel for you?
"他最好不要太久  因为我不知道东西藏哪儿了..."
He better not be long, 'cause I don't know where the stash is...
"要是他们一路带我们穿过这城市"
And if they dragging us all over this part of town--
"那是什么?"
What's that?
天啊
Jesus.
- "不对劲" - "什么"
- Something ain't right. - What?
- "他妈的不对劲" - 老天
- This shit ain't right. - Christ.
"求救! 求救!"
Signal 13, signal 13.
"他妈的怎么搞的"
What the fuck?
她够不着枪
She can't reach the gun.
"他妈的怎么搞的? "两名男性 黑色兜帽 两个都是 "
- What the fuck? - Two males, black hoodies, both of them--
"其中一个..."
one is--
关掉 关掉
Shut it off. Shut it off.
Mells医生 6号线
Dr. Mells, Line 6.
听我说 你操蛋的
Listen to me, you fuck.
你干过很多混账事
You did a lot of shit here.
你他妈的耍过很多鬼把戏 让很多人
You played a lot of fucking cards and made a lot of people...
做了很多他们并不想做的操蛋事
Do a lot of fucking things they didn't want to do.
这是事实
This is true.
我俩都知道这是事实
We both know this is true.
Ralston医生 请呼叫心脏科
Dr. Ralston, please call cardiology.
你 McNulty 是个大混蛋
You, McNulty, are a gaping asshole.
我俩都清楚
We both know this.
刑侦科有谁它妈的不清楚?
Fuck if everybody in CID doesn't know it.
可是它妈的 我才不会站在这里
But fuck if I'm gonna stand here...
指责你它妈的害一名警察了中枪
And say you did a single fucking thing to get a police shot.
不是你 你它妈的听到没?
You did not do this, you fucking hear me?
- 这帐不算你头上 - 嗯
- This is not on you. - yeah.
不 不是你 混球
No, it isn't, asshole.
信不信由你 地球不是围着你转
Believe it or not, everything isn't about you.
说这话的混蛋...
And the motherfucker saying this...
他对你恨之入骨 McNulty
He hates your guts, McNulty.
所以真是你害的
So you know if it was on you...
我一定会是告诉你的那个混蛋
I'd be the son of a bitch to say so.
出了岔子
Shit went bad.
她为行动组吃了两抢
She took two for the company.
这是唯一的教训
That's the only lesson here.
警察!
Police!
警察 把手举起来 趴在地上!
Police, let me see your hands. Get on the ground!
趴在地上!
Down on the ground!
搜捕令 趴在地上
Search warrant, get on the ground.
警察 趴下
Police, get down.
举起手来
Let's see your hands.
- 他不在这里! - 谁不在这里?
- He ain't here! - Who ain't here?
- Zach 他不在这里! - Zach?
- Zach, he ain't here! - Zach?
不 亲爱的 我们找Savino
No, honey, we're looking for Savino.
Savino?
不会的 他是我的宝贝儿子
No, he's my baby.
没错 你的宝贝儿子开枪打了一名警察
Yeah, your baby shot a cop.
他们破门而入 搜捕Savino
They're kicking in the doors, looking for Savino.
什么 怎么回事 哥们?
What? What up with that, man?
说什么他杀了一个警察
Some shit about he killed a cop.
谁 Savino? Savino才没有杀过什么警察
Who, Savino? Savino ain't shot no cop.
他们破门而入 搞得好像是真的
They kicking in the doors, acting like he did it.
- 他妈的 - 我就跟你说嘛 哥们
- Shit. - I'm telling you, man.
无论如何 他们在谈论了
They're talking about it anyway.
一石激起千层浪
Ripples in the pond.
谈论并不代表知情  是吗
Talking ain't knowing, is it?
从另一个角度剖析
Skin this cat another way.
今晚Stringer被呼了两次 对吧
Two pages to Stringer tonight, right?
只有这一次是在枪击以后
Only this one after the shooting.
谁是07
Who's 07?
还有他叫Stringer回复哪个电话亭
And what phone is he asking for Stringer to call him back?
- 事情进展顺利 只是... - 等等
- Shit went good, but-- - Hold on.
"警官在今晨12:30左右中枪"
Officer was shot around 12.:30 this morning.
"警官可能是便衣"
The officer may have been undercover.
- 好了 说吧 - 就像我说的 事情顺利...
- All right, talk. - Like I said, it went good...
只是有个婊子蜷缩在后座上
Except there was this bitch curled up in the back seat.
把我们的魂都吓掉了
Surprised the shit out of us.
要不是她起身都看不见她
Didn't even see her until the shit popped off.
我是说要是我 我就放那妞走了
I mean if it was up to me, I'd have let the girl walk.
她看上去不像长舌妇
She didn't look like the talking type.
可是Little Man见了她 狂性大发 就开了几枪
But Little Man seen her, bugged out, and let a couple go.
- Savino没有警告你们她在那里? - 没时间啊
- Savino didn't tip y'all off to her? - Wasn't no time for that.
他下了车 我们看着他沿着街区走
He get up out the car, we see him go up the block
就像我们约好的一样 是吧
like we said, right?
然后 他走得没影了 我们就照计划行动了 哥们
After that, he out of sight and we bring it home like we planned, baby.
马子是条子
Shorty was a cop.
而且她没死
And she ain't dead.
你们都把枪放哪儿了
Where'd you all put the guns?
她才不是条子呢 哥们 她看上去像Orlando的婊子
She wasn't no cop, man. She look like one of Orlando's hos.
Bey 他妈的枪都在哪儿呢
Bey, where the fuck are the guns?
Park Heights的一个暴雨排水管 哥们
A storm drain off of Park Heights, man.
他妈的Little Man是怎么搞的
What the fuck is wrong with Little Man?
我是说 这操蛋的逃亡过一次
I mean, this motherfucker bugged out one time.
等他发现马子是个他妈的条子时 还要再跑路吗?
He gonna bug out again, when he find out shorty's a fucking cop?
我是说 得了吧 哥们
I mean, come on, man.
Savino可以死咬一个说法 他知道这一点
Savino got a story that he can keep to and he know it...
但是Little Man它妈的没一点种
But Little Man, he always been fucking weak like that.
Little Man得"走人"
Little Man gotta go.
嘿 你听到了吗
You hear me?
这鸟事会变得很严重
This shit gonna get real heavy.
明白吧 我们得避一避风头
You understand me? We gotta fall back.
我想看看Savino那边会怎样发展
I wanna see how it go with this Savino bullshit...
看看条子们怎么处理
See how they go past that.
但如果他的说法出了漏洞
But if the shit don't hold...
或如果这个操蛋的条子醒过来 开口说话
Or if this motherfucking cop wake up and start talking shit...
那你就得跑路了
Then you gotta go sky up.
你在哪里有熟人
Where you got your peoples at?
纽约
New York.
新泽西 克利夫兰
Jersey, Cleveland.
行 那么 费城
All right. So, Philly.
华盛顿 明白我的意思吗
DC. You know what I'm saying?
没有前科 行外人 更不会声张
No profile, no connections, no noise.
你明白我的意思吧
You feel me, right?
好了 我们得小心点
All right. We gotta be careful.
老天啊
Jesus.
听着 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
没关系 只是吓到我了
It's all right, you just scared me.
我是Kima的同事
I work with Kima.
Kima 她....
Kima, she....
Kima上班去了
Kima's at work.
她怎么了?
What is she?
给听筒 退币口和金属箱顶刷粉取指纹
Dust the receiver, the coin return, and the metal top.
还有这易拉罐
The can, too.
Jones医生请到护士站来
Dr. Jones to the nurses' station, please.
我们还不能确定
We can't really know for sure.
队长
Lieutenant.
我陪Kima的姑娘坐在那里
I'm sitting over there with Kima's girl and--
或许局里的人 或市里来的人
Maybe somebody from the department or the city...
想要对她说点什么
Maybe might want to say something.
她的家人有谁来了?
Who's here from the family?
- 你是说女儿吗? - 女儿?
- A daughter, you say? - A daughter?
Greggs警官有个姑娘?
Officer Greggs has a girl?
是室友
A roommate.
她的家人在Richmond 今天第一时间就开车往这里赶
The family's in Richmond, driving up first thing today...
但是室友已经到了
But the roommate's already here.
我自己来吧
I'll do it myself.
没关系
No problem.
如果我们失去了她 他还可以在葬礼上装样子
If we lose her, he can always pose for the funeral.
还是没找到Savino的确切下落
Still need the right door for Savino.
他最后已知的所在地 女友 母亲 都是空巢
His last knowns, his girlfriend, his mama, all empty holes.
痕迹科在一个兜帽里找到几根毛发
Tracers picked up a of couple hairs on one of the hoodies.
不赖嘛
That's something.
所以 要么这些人是附近的混混
So, either these guys are neighborhood yos...
在街上幸运地抢了3万美金 要么...
Who lucked into $30,000 on a street stickup, or....
要么他们是专业杀手 在一头的巷子里杀人
Or they're pros who set up in an alley on one side of the tracks...
然后溜上停在另一头的车跑路
Then slip over to the other side where they park their ride.
鉴证报告呢
What about the post?
Blocker先生的死亡原因和方式是他杀
Cause and manner of death on Mr. Blocker is homicide...
即 近距离枪伤 打中肩膀
To wit, close-range GSWs to the shoulder,
胸部和左臂
Chest and left arm.
9毫米 六道左旋槽 适合作对照
Nine millimeter, six left twist, suitable for comparison.
和我们从汽车后座取出的子弹并不一样 是吧
We pulled something else from the back seat of the car, right?
嗯 那是点38 半被甲弹 弹壳也不同
Yeah, .380. Semi-jacketed. Casings were different, too.
所以我们能确认有两名枪手
So, we confirmed the two shooters.
指纹
Print hit.
Wynton "Little Man" Rice 221大楼的管理者...
Wynton "Little Man" Rice, enforcer in the 221...
绝对和Barksdale的组织有联系
A definite connect to Barksdale's world.
指纹?
Print hit?
哪儿来的指纹?
Print hit from what?
汽水罐
Soda can.
被扔在Park Heights 和Belvedere交接的公用电话旁
Dropped at the pay phone at Park Heights and Belvedere.
我赶到那里时还在冒泡呢
Still had a little fizz in it when I got there.
Park Heights和Belvedere交接的这个公用电话怎么了
What is this pay phone at Park Heights and Belvedere?
有个混蛋在那里呼叫Stringer Bell
It's from which some motherfucker paged Stringer Bell...
枪击发生20分钟之后
20 minutes after the shooting.
我也给话筒刷粉取指纹了 可是已经模糊了
I dusted the phone, too, but it was smudged.
所以说一名Barksdale团伙的专业罪犯
So we got a Barksdale pro in the northwest...
完事后在西北片向打电话给老板
Ringing up the boss minutes after the deed.
"业余者理论"就这样寿终正寝了
So much for the amateur-hour theory.
干得好 你是?
Good pull. You are?
Freamon Lester Freamon
Freamon. Lester Freamon.
你在哪个部门工作
Where you working?
质押组
Pawn shop unit.
我是说 你怎么会向警察开枪呢
I mean, how you gonna shoot a police?
根本没有胜算 懂我的意思吗
Ain't no percentage in that, know what I'm saying?
千真万确
For real.
要是这儿有人这么干
Someone around here do that shit...
世上所有的缉毒条子都会到这里来抓人
Every narco in the world be down here busting heads.
我猜Park Heights那的人就他妈的没啥常识
I guess them Park Heights niggers just ain't got no fucking common sense.
心思活 就是没常识
A lotta heart, just no sense.
Poot
Poot.
Wallace的电话
Wallace on the phone.
- 是吗 - Wallace?
- Yeah? - Wallace?
这小子一天给我两通电话  也不管有话没话
Nigger ring me up twice a day whether he got shit to say or not.
操蛋的想家了 烦都烦死了
Homesick motherfucker making me bug.
他在哪呢?
Where's he at?
在海滨 他外婆那边 在那里...
At the shore with his grandma, down there....
冲浪啥的劳什子
Surfing or some bullshit.
诸如此类的
Or something.
Zellesky医生 5号线有您的电话
Dr. Zellesky, you have a call on Line 5.
你刚用了那个电话?
You just use that phone?
嗯 前些时候 你或许可以去Mosher街
Yeah, a little earlier. You might wanna go to Mosher Street.
就刚才 你用了吗
Just now, you used it?
嗯
Yeah.
市局里有人要和你谈话
A man downtown needs to talk to you.
市局里的人?
Man downtown?
和这个人讲讲道理 拜托了 好吗
Make some sense for this man, please. All right?
我这辈子从来没有这样远离毒品
I ain't never been so clean in my life.
我只是履行我的职责
I'm just doing my job.
好吧
Okay.
怎么了 海滩地产先生?
What up, Mr. Beachfront Property?
不是啦 傻瓜 我告诉过你 我在海湾边
No, fool, I told you, I'm bayside.
我祖母在海湾边
My grandmother on the bayside.
不过 你还是没带上我就去度假了 哥们
Still, man, you on vacation and not bringing me with you.
你一路怎么过去的?
How you get all the way down there?
坐公交
I took a bus.
妈的 告诉我怎么走 我再带上一猎狗
Shit, tell me how to go, and I grab a 'hound, too.
过去你那里 和你一起混
Come down there and hang with your ass.
不行 哥们 不是这样的  这里的空气很潮湿
No, man, it ain't like that. The air down here all sticky.
比Baltimore还糟
Worse than Baltimore.
还有这些蟋蟀 比操蛋的还聒噪
And these crickets, louder than a motherfucker.
搞得我都睡不着
I can't get no sleep.
我想我注定不是个乡下人 哥们
I don't think I'm cut out to be no country-ass nigger, man.
继续通话2分钟 请再投入2美元
Please deposit two dollars for an additional two minutes.
妈的 我要挂了
Shit, I gotta go.
你可以把一个黑佬从西区带走 但是你不能带...
You can take a nigger out the Westside. But you can't take--
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
听着 我没犯事 好吗
Look, I didn't do shit here, okay?
我问你的名字
I asked you your name.
不 这样没道理
No, this shit ain't right.
你在呼谁呢 鸟人?
Who'd you try to page, shit bird?
关你屁事 啊? 我是说....
Why the fuck do you care, okay? I mean....
你还有三秒钟解释给我听 混蛋
You have exactly three more seconds to explain yourself to me, asshole.
一名枪手明显打开过乘客门...
One shooter definitely opened the passenger door...
因此车上那一块任何潜在的指纹....
So any latent prints from that side of the car....
- 你为什么呼她 鸟人? - 走开
- Why'd you page her, shit bird? - Get off me.
你觉得这他妈的是个游戏吗
You think this is a fucking game?
- 我想和Greggs警探说话 - 不行 操蛋的
- I wanna talk to Detective Greggs. - You can't, motherfucker.
那就McNulty 他妈的没道理 警官
Then McNulty then. This shit ain't right, sir.
Savino
Savino.
这毒贩不在附近
Mope ain't around.
一个平房区的小喽啰在用高楼区2号电话亭
One of them low-rise hoppers on Tower Phone 2.
好的
Okay.
可能他忘了号码
Maybe he forgot the number.
他妈的那是咋回事
The fuck was that?
你不知道?
You don't know?
我们刚目睹了高楼区藏毒点的补货
We just caught a re-up off the tower stash.
4楼 南边 第二间
Fourth floor, south side, second unit down.
把那东西收起来
Put that away.
把那东西收起来 专心破案
Put that away and work the case.
我能问你一句话吗
Can I ask you something?
这案子 你愿意放弃多少 来挽回她?
How much of this case would you give up to get her back?
那不是重点
That's not the point.
多少?
How much?
全部
All of it.
但事情不能那样解决
But it doesn't work that way.
换不回来
You can't give it back.
我这里有一份医院进展报告
I'm sitting with a hospital progress report
上面他妈的一点进展都没有
That shows no fucking progress.
她昏迷不醒 插着通气管
She's not conscious, she's intubated.
实施了气管切开术  伴有肺萎陷...
She's had a trach and a lung collapse...
要是她有一丁点运气
And if she's got a shred of luck...
脖子上中的那枪就不会打在脊椎上了
The shot she took to the neck didn't catch any spine.
这不值得
It wasn't worth it.
凶杀科找McNulty 二号线
Homicide for McNulty on Line 2.
干活吧
Do your job.
喂?
Yeah?
你还好吗
So how you doing with it?
死不了
I'll live.
是吗?
Yeah?
听着 Jimmy
Listen, Jimmy.
我们这里刚有场小骚乱
We had a little dust-up over here.
Holley为了碰运气 可能打了一个你姑娘的线人
Holley might have beat one of your girl's Cls on spec.
他什么样 矮个子? 话很多?
What is he, a short guy? Mumbles a lot?
嗯 就是他
Yeah, that's him.
你或许想过来 遏止这鸟事
You might wanna roll past and squelch this shit...
以防事态失控
Before it gets outta hand.
嗯
Yeah.
真不值 哥们
It ain't worth it, man.
就算10倍的价格也不值
It ain't worth it at 10 times the price.
一个鸟警察 哥们 一个警察! 这操蛋的有多蠢
A fucking cop, man. A cop! How stupid is this motherfucker?
如果在车里看到一马子 改变计划
Lf you see a bitch in the car, change it up.
他妈的我们可以改天再做了Orlando
We can go to Orlando another fucking day.
Savino说他试着示意他们  但是他在黑暗中
Savino say he was trying to signal, but he in the dark...
他不知道Bey会从哪里出现
He don't know where Bey's coming from.
我们还真不走运 靠
Nothing breaking our way, man, damn.
我们得烧掉这玩意儿 这是警察的钱
We gotta burn this shit. This is cop money.
肯定用某种方式做了记号
It's probably marked somehow.
枪在下水管道里 Bey很可靠 所以没关系
The guns are in the sewer, Bey's a rock, so that's cool.
但那个贱人警察 如果她开口说话
But it's the bitch cop. If she starts talking,
她会把Little Man和Bey都弄进去
She gonna put Little Man and Bey in there.
Little Man怎么样了
What up with Little Man?
- 他吓得要死 他开枪打了个警察 - 操
- He's scared. He shot a cop. - Fuck.
但是我交给Bey去处理了
But I put Bey on that.
那么Savino呢
What about Savino?
Savino他得吃官司
Savino, he gotta eat the charge.
可是他知道的
But he knew that.
所以如果他死咬他的说法 他就会没事
So if he keep his story tight, he gonna be all right.
我们知道Orlando是个操蛋的告密者 哥们
We knew Orlando was a snitching motherfucker, man.
去他的 但是这些是现金 他让我们麻烦大了
Fuck him, but this is cash. He got us caught up.
我知道 哥们 是我的错 哥们
I know, man. That's my fault, man.
Bey和Savino向我提出...
Bey and Savino came to me with the idea that...
如果他们做掉Orlando 他们也可以带走现金
If they take Orlando, they can take the cash, too.
我就说 行啊 是该拿点报酬...
I was like, all right, you all get your payday--
Orlando怎么会预付这种钱
How the fuck is Orlando gonna front this type of cash?
这说明了什么?
What it say?
我知道
I know.
我知道 我搞砸了
I know, I fucked up.
好了把这垃圾拿到外面去 他妈的烧了
All right, take this trash outside, fucking burn it.
叫Wee-Bey在跑路前收拾残局
Tell Wee-Bey to clean up the mess before he jet.
他给她呼机发了紧急传呼
He was throwing 911 messages to her pager.
我问他为什么
I asked him why.
他顶嘴了
He raised up.
事态就失控了
Shit got outta hand.
他知道了吗
Does he know?
McNulty 哥们 他们那是干嘛呢 哥们?
McNulty, man. What they doing over there, man?
他就这样开始暴打我
He just started beating on me.
昨晚 她遭到枪击
Last night, she got shot.
当时他妈的你在哪里
Where the fuck were you at?
- 你在哪里? - 我就在那里
- Where were you? - I was there.
Bunk
Bunk.
Holley在调查
Holley is investigating.
我们在乘客门上没找到指纹
We got no good latents on the passenger side door.
...然后他看到她寻呼机上的急呼
...and he sees her pager coming up 911 .
仪表盘呢
What about the dash?
你得帮帮我!
You gotta help me!
打电话给实验室问呗
Call the lab.
那么她受伤了 我能做什么?
So, what can I do?
一来你可以在公房区转转 看看谁不见了
For one thing you can roll around the projects and see who's missing.
谁不在了
Who ain't around.
这样做得到吗
You okay with that?
嗯 只是....
Yeah, I just....
我最近有些走上正道了 你知道吗?
I been keeping it kinda close, you know?
最近不怎么去公房区了
Ain't been around the projects much lately.
你懂我的意思吗?
You know what I'm saying?
和那里的人结仇了?
You beefing with someone down there?
不 我没有结仇...
No, I'm not beefing with....
睁大眼睛 Bubbs
Eyes open, Bubbs.
为了Kima
For Kima.
别担心 我开车送你
Hang loose, I'll get you a ride.
Savino的下落如何?
Where are we with Savino?
还是不见踪影
Still MIA.
受够了这样的废话
Enough of this bullshit.
如果他打电话找我 我会叫他自首的
If he calls me for anything, I'll tell him to turn himself in.
- 我会的 - 这不够
- I'm going to do that. - Not good enough.
对不起 你说什么?
Excuse me?
我们现在就要他
We need him now.
不用 谢谢
No, thanks.
或许作为法庭官员...
Perhaps as an officer of the court...
Ronnie表现得彬彬有礼
Ronnie here is being polite.
她是你们畸形部落中的一员
She's a member of your twisted little tribe.
她用的是你们的小小畸形语言 我嘛?
She's putting it into your twisted little language. Me?
我擦屁股都会不用Baltimore的律师
I wouldn't wipe my ass with a Baltimore lawyer.
无意冒犯
No offense.
没关系
None taken.
我是说 我愿意 让你们这些小操蛋的教唆人做伪证...
I mean, I'm willing to let you little ratfuckers suborn perjury...
向法官煽风点火 一个劲儿地贿赂陪审团...
Blow smoke up a judge's ass and jury-tamper your balls off...
一点也影响不了我的阳光性格
Without losing the slightest bit of my sunny s
我也不会不让你把现金 伪装成办公费
Fuck me if I don't let you structure your cash into briefcase fees, either.
那是你和国税局之间的事 你们俩都不是任何人的朋友 对吧?
That's between you and the IRS. Neither one of you is anyone's friend, right?
Jimmy 想说的是...
What Jimmy is trying to say is--
不 Jimmy想说的是 如果你想让我对你的鸟事睁一只眼闭一只眼
No, what Jimmy is saying is if you want my nose closed to your shit...
那在我有需要的时候 你得给我点甜头
You have to throw me something when I need it.
眼下我需要带着手铐的Savino Bratton
And right now I need Savino Bratton in bracelets.
我不知道他在哪里
I don't know where he is.
最近四宗大罪你都代表他出庭
You repped him the last four felonies.
我想如果你想传消息一定传得到
I guess you can get word to him if you want to.
一名警察可能会死 Morrie 而Savino就在现场
A police may die, Morrie, and Savino was there.
他今天下午来警局...
He comes in this afternoon...
至少吃毒品官司
And he takes the drug charge at least.
否则?
Or what?
否则我们每天晚上派特警队去他妈妈家...
Or we send tactical teams into his momma's house every night...
直到把那拆得片甲不留
Until there's no house left to worry about.
在传唤作证之前 要求证人提供个人背景资料
你会收到州检察院发的证人信...
You get a target letter from the state's attorney's office...
而传唤你名下所有银行账单的传票 也会接踵而至
Followed by subpoenas for every bank account in your fucking name.
然后让我们看看那些存款 是不是都和上报的收入相符
And let's see if all those cash deposits match the reported income.
他的话我听到了...
I'm hearing this from him...
我知道他情绪失控...
And I understand that he's distraught.
我能理解
I understand that.
州检察院也是这样的意见吗?
Am I hearing this from the state's attorney's office as well?
是的
You are.
我尽力而为
I'll see what I can do.
去你的 Jimmy!
Fuck you, Jimmy!
- 你没告诉我你会来这一手 - 他会把他带来的
- You didn't tell me that was coming. - He'll bring him in.
如果他能当然会带来 这不是重点
He will if he can, that's not the point.
那什么是重点
What's the point?
重点是Morrie Levy
The point is that Morrie Levy is a past officer
是前任律师协会官员...
Of the Monumental Bar Association...
除非我想一辈子做一个他妈的州检察官...
And unless I want to spend my whole life as a fucking ASA...
我不能一下午招惹重要人物
I can't spend my afternoons pissing on people who matter.
又是一个悬而未决的职业生涯
Another career in the balance.
- 你去死吧 - 不 是你去死吧
- Fuck you. - No, fuck you.
要是你们这些检察院狗娘养的人里有一半...
If only half of you in the state's attorney's office...
不想当法官...
Didn't want to be judges...
不想在城里的律师公司做合伙人...
Didn't want to be partners in a downtown law firm...
如果你们有勇气查到底 你知道会发生什么吗
If you had the balls to follow through, you know what would happen?
像那样的人会被起诉 审判并定罪
A guy like that would be indicted, tried and convicted.
其余这样的人就会往后缩...
The rest of them would back up...
这样我们就可以在你们的法庭上 打一宗干干净净的案子
So we could push a clean case through your courthouse.
但是不行 所有人都是朋友  所有人都有钱拿
But no, everybody stays friends. Everybody gets paid.
而且所有人都有他妈的未来
And everybody's got a fucking future.
你谁都可以利用 是吧
You'll just use anyone, won't you?
我一直在日志里查
I've been searching the logs
使用07代码的寻呼机号码 对吧?
For pager hits that used an 07 code, right?
D'Angelo的寻呼机里时常会出现
It comes up now and then on D'Angelo's pager.
还有Stringer的 但没那么频繁
Stringer's, too, but less often.
大多数时候 没法定位这个人..
Most of the time, there's nothing to place the guy...
可你瞧
But check it.
这是Stringer寻呼机上的?
And this is on Stringer's page?
回电到马里兰大医院里
It comes back to the pay phone in the emergency room
急诊室的公用电话
At Maryland General Hospital.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
这次呼叫的日期和Stinkum被杀是同一天
The date of this page is the same day that Stinkum got killed.
还有Wee-Bey腿上中枪
And Wee-Bey got shot in the leg.
至少监听线上是这样说的
That was the talk on the wire, anyway.
如果你去马里兰大医院
If you go to Maryland General
把那天早上的急诊室记录调出来...
And pull the ER records for that morning...
你会发现Wee-Bey在里面
You're gonna find Wee-Bey in the pile.
"07"是Wee-Bey 一定是的
07 is Wee-Bey.It's gotta be.
我们发现了Wee-Bey和Little Man
And we have Wee-Bey and Little Man
在伏击20分钟后 用Park Heights的公用电话
At the pay phone at Park Heights 20 minutes after the ambush...
呼叫Stringer
Throwing a page to Stringer.
我们全城热搜狗娘养的Savino
We're all over town for this piece-of-shit Savino.
他和Barksdale组织有关?
With ties to the Barksdale organization?
- 是的 长官 - 还有别的吗?
- Yes, sir. - What else?
案子有进展
The case is progressing.
我们从监听线上获知枪击嫌犯
We're gleaning possible shooters from the wiretap.
是我要求这次诱买
I asked for the controlled buy.
我让一名我们的同事受了伤
I put one of our people in harm's way.
所以现在我想确保我们在尽一切努力
So right now I want to make sure that we are doing everything.
- 是的 长官 我们在办 - 很好
- We are, sir, we're on it. - Good.
长官想要全市性的突袭
The commissioner wants raids citywide.
所有能进去的门 所有能写下的地址
Every door we can take. Any addresses we can write on,
任何与缉毒案有关的东西
Anything connected to a narcotics case.
刑侦部 特警队 缉毒组...
CID, tactical, the DEUs...
明天 在6:00新闻...
And tomorrow, on the 6:00 news...
我们把他妈的一大堆毒品摆在桌子上
We put a lot of fucking dope on the table.
一大堆
A lot of it.
毒品摆桌上?
Dope on the table?
我们需要让他们知道我们是谁
We need to let them know who we are.
我们一分钟都不能让他们 以为这种事可以继续
We can't for one minute let them think that this will stand.
长官想要传达一种信息 中尉
The Commissioner wants to send a message, Lieutenant.
你确保你和你的人...
You make sure you and your people...
尽其所能传播这条信息
Do everything possible to see that it is heard.
他妈的毒品摆桌上
Dope on the damn table.
就像他说的
It's like the man said.
我们要让他们知道我们是谁
We're letting them know who we are.
是吗 那他妈的我们是谁呢
Yeah? And who the hell are we?
再正式重申一次
Again, for the record,
米兰达原则：疑犯享有的权力
让我们明确Bratton先生 没有被告知米兰达原则...
Let's make clear that Mr. Bratton has not been Mirandized...
并且在这里说的话都是自愿提供
And that what is said here is for purposes of a proffer.
- 同意吗 - 同意
- Agreed? - Agreed.
好的 那么
Okay, then.
给你
Here you go.
这是烘焙苏打
That's baking soda.
Bratton先生企图把这个 贩卖给Orlando Blocker
Which Mr. Bratton intended to sell to Orlando Blocker.
你们可以留着 我们免费奉上
You can keep it with our compliments.
钱在哪里
Where's the money?
Bratton先生没有拿到钱
Mr. Bratton did not receive money.
当他去取假可卡因时把它留在车里了
He left it in the car when he went to retrieve the sham cocaine.
如果你们录下交易的话 磁带会核实这一点
If you were recording the transaction, the tape will confirm this.
枪击发生时他也不在
And he wasn't around for the shooting either.
事实上 他不知道枪手是谁
He doesn't know who the shooters are.
天知道他其实没有参与伏击
And God knows he wasn't in on the setup.
我是说 他让他们留在死胡同里
I mean, it was pure dumb luck...
结果他们两分钟以后遇害... 完全是因为运气坏到了家
That he left them in an dead-end alley and they were shot just two minutes later.
真是胡扯
This is bullshit.
一个警察倒下了
A police is down.
Bratton先生并不知晓
Mr. Bratton had no knowledge
那位年轻女子是警官
That the young woman was a police officer.
并且除了诈骗Blocker先生3万美元之外 别无企图
And no intention of doing anything other than defrauding Mr. Blocker of $30,000.
Nathan女士?
Ms. Nathan?
如果他供出枪击者就不予定罪
No charge if he gives us the shooters.
如果他作证 我们会找到办法
And if he testifies we'll find a way
让他加入联邦证人计划
To squeeze him into the federal witness program.
正如我指出的那样
As I indicated...
Bratton先生不知道谁枪击了Blocker先生...
Mr. Bratton has no idea who shot Mr. Blocker...
和便衣警官
Or the undercover officer.
你最多能整个286B
Best you can do is 286B.
那是啥玩意儿
What the hell is that?
散布山寨管制危险品
Distribution of sham CDS.
最长刑期3年 罚款5000美元
Three-year maximum, $5,000 fine.
就这些?
That's it?
如果他拿了现金 我们可以定个盗窃或诈骗重罪...
If he took the cash, we could go to felony theft or fraud...
但是磁带表明他没拿钱
But the tape has him leaving the money.
3年
Three years.
一名警察被枪击了 Morrie
A cop was shot, Morrie.
所以如果我们判他有罪 他会结结实实地坐上3年牢
So if we convict, he'll do every damn day of the three.
我可以蹲三年 没什么大不了
I can do the three. Ain't no thing.
那5000美元罚款呢
And the $5,000 fine?
妈的 你还是剩了2万5 对吧
Shit, you still up $25,000, right?
干得真不赖
Nicely done.
给我两个
Give me two.
该死 Orlando
Damn, Orlando.
我还是不敢相信
I still can't believe that shit.
哥们 这些破事都和这操蛋的有关
Man, all this shit behind this motherfucker.
他妈的他到底是谁
Who the fuck was he?
他为我舅舅经营一家俱乐部
He ran a club for my uncle.
是吗
Yeah?
嗯 先是Stink 现在又是他
Yeah, first Stink, and now him.
是啊 哥们 还有我听说警察们 都在找Savino的麻烦
Yeah, man, and I heard the cops been all in Savino's shit, too.
- 他最近都不在这里 - Little Man也不在
- He ain't been around. - Little Man, neither.
得有人出来搞定这鸟事啊
Somebody could get to cleaning up shit around here.
没错
True.
你不能这样到处放倒条子啊
You can't just be going around, dropping 5-0 like that.
你知道当人们办砸事时 你舅舅是怎样的反应 哥们
You know how your uncle is when people get to fucking up, man.
他会把事情看做个人恩怨 哥们
He starts taking that shit personal, man.
看上去还要挂几个家伙
Look like a couple more niggers gonna get dropped.
- 咋了 - 你是Dee吗
- What up? - You Dee?
对
Yeah.
他们说你得马上去找Stringer 立刻就去
They say you need to get with Stringer, right away.
听到了吧
See?
你升官儿啦
You moving up in the world.
只要你不要成为他们清理的垃圾就行
As long as you don't fall in with the trash they taking out.
呵 管他呢 小子
Yeah, whatever, nigger.
我去去就来
I'll be right back.
高楼区的人都紧张得不得了
Tower boys all nervous and shit.
Little Man没来上班
Little Man ain't post for work.
而且也不回传呼
Ain't answering his page, neither.
瞧
See?
我不准备说谎
I'm not gonna lie.
她椎骨附近浮肿...
She has swelling around the vertebrae...
并且有局部瘫痪的迹象
And some indications of partial paralysis.
这种症状会不会在浮肿消退后消失 还不知道
That may or may not go away when the swelling goes down.
她家人在陪着她
Her family is with her.
凶杀科他妈的是怎么搞的
What the fuck is up with Homicide?
我们开始调查枪手了吗
Are we on the shooters yet?
他们在努力工作
They're working it hard.
局里的回应是 明天一早入户搜查
The departmental response is gonna be to take doors tomorrow morning.
在全市范围内
Citywide.
每个小队 每个区的警察都会闯入...
Every unit, every district is kicking in...
能写得出来的任何和毒品有关的地址
Any drug-connected address they can write on.
我们也要这样做
We're gonna do the same.
- 队长 这是不是... - 除了...
- Lieutenant, is that-- - Except...
我们会放过他们的老窝
We're gonna hold back on the main stash.
我们在监听线上追踪到的 那栋西北边的房子...
The house up in northwest we tracked off the wire....
一来守着那个地方还能使案子有更多进展
We advance this case more by sitting on that location.
二来如果突袭太百发百中了...
And raids that are too much on the bulls-eye...
Barksdale就会改变策略
Will have Barksdale changing up.
监听线可能就废了
We might blow the wire altogether.
我们有两个平房区的可能藏毒地址...
We got two addresses in the low-rises that are probables...
还有远离大道的两排房屋
And another two row houses off the avenue
就在上周 曾经被用来藏毒
That have been used for stash as recently as last week.
但是这个....
But this....
这是大丰收的不二之选
This here is the best bet for a good rip.
Herc昨晚发现的
Herc picked up on it yesterday.
四楼...
Fourth-floor...
221大楼南面最后的单元
End unit on the south side of the 221 .
他们把补货扔出窗外给小喽啰 然后小喽啰拿着补货闪人
They're dropping the re-ups out the window to the hoppers who run it off.
要是他们更换公寓怎么办
What if they change up the apartment?
他们每天都换
They do that every day.
昨天是5楼北面
Yesterday was the fifth floor on the north side.
我们让一个人带着手机在教堂顶盯梢
We'll have a man on the church with a cell phone.
他们换了
They change up,
我们致电值班法官 法官口头修改搜查令
We call the duty judge who orally amends the warrant.
我们11:00开始突袭
We hit everything at 11:00.
负责高楼区的小队需要5:00开始
The squad that takes the high-rise needs to stage at 5:00.
我们需要在大楼里的人睡醒前进去
We need to be inside before the building even wakes up.
要是今晚还想睡觉
Anyone who wants to sleep tonight
就得马上开始打字
Needs to start typing his ass off right now.
咋了
What's up?
俱乐部怎么不开了
Why ain't the club open?
你和Bey走一趟
You going with Bey.
嘿 Bey
Bey.
手脚麻利点
Keep it clean.
别出什么差错
Don't make no mistakes.
去哪里
Going where?
他妈的你还等什么?
What the fuck you waiting for?
别跟我胡扯了
Stop bullshitting me.
那个老窝
The main stash.
他知道我们在查
He knows we're on it.
他知道我们隐瞒了
He knows we held it back.
副局
The Deputy.
我们在公房区抓了个 带着一袋钱的议员的人 他知道
We grab a senator's bag man in the projects, he knows that.
州警局带来个合作者 他也知道
State Police bring in a cooperator, he knows it, too.
还真他妈的及时
Like fucking clockwork.
他一定有眼线
He's got a rat.
就在专案组里
Here, in the detail.
起初...
In the beginning...
我们刚刚开始时 我对Burrell忠心耿耿
When we started, Burrell had me.
我把一切都告诉那个操蛋的
I pipelined everything to that motherfucker.
可现在你背弃了他
But now he lost you.
所以现在他又选了一个
So now he's picked up someone else.
他们都这么干
That's how they do.
支持民主...   投票...
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
失陪一会儿 先生们
Excuse me a moment, gentlemen.
是Burrell 他得歇歇手
It's Burrell, he's gotta back off already.
又怎么了
What now?
我们在查一个主要藏毒点 Barksdale的老窝
We're on a prime location. Barksdale's stash.
他想让我们写一份文件 破门而入 而不是立案
Instead of making cases, he wants us to write a paper and take the door.
- 为什么 - 毒品摆桌上
- Why? - Dope on the table.
是个摆门面的行动 就为了让我们
It's a photo op to make us feel better about Kima Greggs
对Kima Greggs吃了几个子弹的事好受些
Catching a bullet or two.
老天
Christ.
你得再给他来一手 法官大人
You need to rip him a new one, Your Honor.
我不知道 Jimmy
I don't know, Jimmy.
你又上选票了 嗯?
You back on the ticket, huh?
就是那点老调子
It was just the usual bullshit.
他们让我四处露面...
They're just dicking me around...
想再让一个黑人上选票 弄成4比1...
Trying to get another black face, make it four-and-one...
这样可以和上次持平
To even up for the last time.
州长得答应两项新职位的任命
The Governor had to promise two new appointments.
所以现在我们又回到了起点
So now we're back where we were.
仅此而已
That's all it was.
仅此而已?
That's all?
半吊子庸碌政治 Jimmy
Half-assed hack politics, Jimmy.
和你的案子无关
It has nothing to do with your case.
这件事我需要你
I need you on this.
那么 现在谁是我老爹?
So, who's my daddy now?
我只是做他们让我做的鸟事 知道吗
I just do what the fuck they tell me, you know?
我又不知道他们脑子里想的是什么鸟事
It ain't on me to know what the fuck they have in mind.
听着 Bey
Look, Bey.
现在又来了这么件荒唐的破事
Now it come down to this crazy shit.
嘿 开进这个胡同 就这里
Turn in this alley right here. Right there.
他妈的干嘛停下啊 走啊!
What the fuck you stopping for? Go!
进去啊 哥们 走吧
Inside, man. Let's go.
这老兄傻了
This dude is crazy.
进去 混蛋 我们可不能整晚耗在这鸟事上
Get in, motherfucker. We ain't got all night for this shit.
哥们 进来啊
Man, get in here.
走啊 哥们
Go ahead, man.
你犯啥毛病?
What's wrong with you?
瞧瞧 Dee
Check it out, Dee.
我需要你在我离开的时候喂喂它们
I need you to feed them while I'm gone.
每个缸里的鱼给不同的食物 行吗
You gonna give them different food for each tank, too, all right?
可是别担心 我会告诉你怎么做 过来
But don't worry. I'm gonna show you what to do. Come here.
这些是我的脂鲤
These are my Tetras.
有Kimmy Alex Aubrey
You got Kimmy, Alex, Aubrey
还有Jezebel在缸里的某个地方
And Jezebel in here somewhere.
我不知道 她以为自己很靓
I don't know, she think she cute.
你喂两撮我放在每个鱼缸旁的鱼食
You take two pinches of whatever food I got next to each tank.
一天就没问题了
They set for the day.
看到了吧 他们不麻烦
You see, they ain't no problems.
只是漂亮得要命 Dee
Just beautiful as hell, Dee.
我要上楼 打包东西
I'm gonna go upstairs, and pack some shit.
嘿 Bey
Bey.
我们去哪里 哥们?
Where we going, man?
费城 你把卡车开回去...
Philly. You gonna take the truck back...
但是首先我得上楼拿点东西
But first I got to go upstairs, grab some shit,
告诉你怎么摆弄我的鱼缸 对吧
Show you what to do with my tanks, right?
费城?
Philly?
我们枪击了个缉毒科的警察 Dee
We shot a narco, Dee.
Savino不见了
No Savino.
Little Man不见了 Wee-Bey也不见了
No Little Man, no Wee-Bey, either.
还有Pit里那个姓Barksdale的小子...
And the Barksdale kid from the Pit...
他也不在混了
He's out the mix, too.
你觉得是他们干的?
You think it was them that did it?
Wee-Bey  Savino  Little Man
Wee-Bey, Savino, Little Man.
嗯 我们听说的也是这样
Yeah, that's what we're hearing, too.
我们有这些操蛋的消息...
We got pick-ups on these motherfuckers...
还有一大堆国家犯罪信息库的没用东西
And miles of NCIC bullshit.
还有血样和头发采集的许可令
Warrants for blood and hair, too.
是Bey和Little Man 枪手1号和2号 我感觉就是 Bunk
It's Bey and Little Man, shooter one and two. I feel it, Bunk.
是吗
Yeah?
眼下 我们需要我们的姑娘醒来...
Right now, we need our girl to wake up...
告诉我们是这样的
And say so.
好吧
All right.
干得好 Bubbs
You did good, Bubbs.
McNulty 其实...
McNulty, you know...
现在我的情况不同了
The situation is different for me.
我是说 对我来说 我...
I mean, for me, I'm--
行动
Mount up.
我得走了
I gotta go.
Prez会送你一程 行吗
Prez will get you a ride, okay?
行动
Move out.
警察 警察! 走走走!
Police. Police! Go!
举起手来 混蛋!
Show your hands, asshole!
趴到地上 快点 快点!
Down on the ground. Move it, move it!
McNulty  Freamon 检查地下室
McNulty, Freamon, check the basement.
- 没有危险? - 没有危险
- Clear? - All clear.
浴室没有危险
Bathroom's clear.
检查床垫 检查床下 检查所有的抽屉
Check the mattress. Check under the bed, check all the drawers,
检查这个该死的房间的每一寸地方
Check every fucking inch of this room.
- 发现什么了吗? - 没有
- Got anything? - No.
- 中了 - 这是啥
- Bingo. - Look at this.
找到了
Got it.
在这里呢
There she goes.
装起来
Bag it.
来吧
Let's do it.
真是漂亮的行动 Erv
That's fine police work, Erv.
女士们 先生们...
Ladies and gentlemen...
你们在前面这张桌子上所看到的...
What you see on the table in front of you...
代表了我局
Represents our department's answer
对死亡和毒品文化的回应
To a culture of death and drugs.
当一名警官在这场战争中倒下...
And when an officer falls in this war...
其他警官准备好迎接挑战...
Others stand ready to pick up the challenge...
把战斗进行到那些有罪的人门前
And carry the fight to the very doorstep of those responsible.
这只是一个开端 我可以向你们保证
This is only the beginning, I can assure you.
但是今天 信息已经传达出去
But today, a message has been sent.
相信我 那些靠运送和销售毒品...
And believe me, this message is being heard loud and clear...
来谋求金钱和权力的人...
By all those who seek profit and power...
都听得清清楚楚
In the importation and sale of illegal drugs.
进展缓慢
Slow.
McCullough街电话亭都是废话 高楼区什么也没有
Bullshit on the McCullough Street phone, nothing on the towers.
谁在房顶上
Who's on the rooftop?
没有人
No one.
他妈的
Fuck it.
钱在哪儿呢 哥们
Where's the money, man?
- 你需要多少钱 - 公交车费大概18美元 哥们
- How much you need? - The bus cost like $18, man.
你祖母没有吗
Your grandma ain't got it?
如果我向她要 她会不让我订票的
If I ask her, she gonna try to stop me from booking.
我不是和你说嘛 哥们 这种鸟乡村生活搞得我一团糟
I'm telling you, boy. This country-ass shit got me all messed up.
记录:无关
我说你得给我寄点公交车费
I'm saying, you need to send me something for the bus.
我在这儿快死了 都崩溃了
I'm dyin' here, all broke and shit.
嗯 我明白
Yeah, I feel you.
你想什么时候回来
When do you want to come home?
钱寄到就回来
When the money get here.
好的 我可能今天就寄
All right, I'm gonna probably send it today.